

ASHLEY TIEU NGUYEN

CONTACT

832-964-6497 <u>ashley.tieu.nguyen@gmail.com</u> Houston, TX <u>LinkedIn</u>

EDUCATION

UX/UI Bootcamp University of Texas at Austin 2021-Present

Bachelor of Arts, Sociology Minor, Business Foundations University of Texas at Austin 2009-2013

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Miro
- User Experience Research
- User Interface Design
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- User Flows
- Information Architecture
- Microsoft Office
- Data Reporting & Analysis
- SAP
- IPOS
- Pivotal CRM
- Social Media

ABOUT ME

I am currently an Information Security Analyst who is searching to switch my career path to UX/UI Design. Why? It reminded me about why I studied Sociology in the first place. I enjoy studying human social behavior and social interaction. Even though, this is a drastic change from Cybersecurity, I believe my current experience in Information Technology will only be an advantage in the tech industry. I enjoy challenging myself and UX/UI design lights a fire in me to want to grow and learn more about design.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INFORMATION SECURITY ANALYST ASG Technologies | Houston, TX | March 2018 – Present

- Administers the Information Security Management Program
- Information Security & Phishing Awareness Trainings in ASGu
- Phishing simulation campaigns in KnowBe4
- Monthly report of all consolidated security vulnerabilities scans
- Monthly communication to inform machine owners of security vulnerabilities
- Manages all responses to customer security questionnaires and external financial audits for IT controls
- Captures Information Security metrics for ISMT Quarterly Meetings
- Assists with creation of information security advisories and newsletters
- Maintains policy documentation within IT Governance site
- Performs periodic access reviews
- Performs vendor assurance activities

MARKETING ANALYST MICRO FOCUS / NETIQ | Houston, TX | November 2017 – February 2018

- Support the AMS Regional Marketing Team by providing actionable data analysis of data metrics and KPIs, including lead aging and pipeline
- Provide consistent stakeholder communications to the AMS Regional Marketing Team
- Analyze the Wins/Losses of Opportunities in our CRM to gather any trends that led to the end result
- Pull and analyze marketing data on the web & CRM activities of each sales representative's top named accounts
- Assemble scorecards summarizing the sales representative's top named accounts' actions on the web and in our CRM
- Provide reporting to the AMS Regional Marketing Team on budgets and marketing pipeline target goals
- Develop an engaged model for alignment with the Partner Marketing team for Channel and Alliances



ASHLEY TIEU NGUYEN

SPECIAL SKILLS

- Bilingual in English and Vietnamese
- Public Speaking
- Event Planning
- Organizing Fundraisers

ORGANIZATIONS

- Kappa Phi Lambda

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

FIELD MARKETING ASSOCIATE MICRO FOCUS / NETIQ | Houston, TX | May 2015 – October 2017

- Assist Field Marketing Managers in planning and executing demand generation programs such as events, webinars, trade shows, customer dinners, user groups, and technical summits while utilizing the full mix of marketing resources
- Coordinate with the extended marketing teams, sales teams, partner organizations, and key vendors to successfully execute marketing programs and events to acquire leads to add to the marketing pipeline
- Ensure projects and campaigns are created in our Customer Relationship Management software and simultaneously updated on our website to maximize visibility and exposure to potential customers and prospects
- Facilitate lead cleansing and upload process for all campaigns and projects
- Coordinate with Purchasing and Accounting departments to create purchase orders and approve & reconcile invoices
- Prepare and develop quarterly reports detailing campaigns and program performance targets
- Coordinated with the sales teams, campaign marketing teams, and product marketing teams to facilitate and develop a 12-webinar series showcasing Micro Focus's products which was featured in the company's "TechTalks"
- Spearheaded 15 state & local and federal trade shows coordinating with all pertinent teams to secure trade show locations and booths, ensure all relevant marketing resources are available as needed, and facilitate any special and specific needs for each trade show

IT TELECOM EXPENSE ADMINISTRATOR MICRO FOCUS / NETIQ | Houston, TX | March 2014 - May 2015

- Audit, validate and approve Telecom invoices
- Monitor fluctuations in monthly cost and excess charges
- Dispute invoice discrepancies and process requests for credits
- Code and allocate expenses to the appropriate cost center
- Collaborate with Accounts Payable to ensure all Telecom invoices are paid in a timely manner
- Process and track orders for new service, service failures and service disconnect
- Manage voice and data usage on corporate cell phone account
- Assist with Go-To-Meeting and Go-To-Webinar requests